<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home</title>
    <link>https://abrac012.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://abrac012.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Edits to consider</title>
      <link>https://abrac012.github.io/post/post2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abrac012.github.io/post/post2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Okay, so here&amp;rsquo;s what I&amp;rsquo;m thinking&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As far as making a dark theme option, I think the background is already fine for that, but the actual post content isn&amp;rsquo;t. I don&amp;rsquo;t know how to fix that yet, but I&amp;rsquo;m sure there&amp;rsquo;s some sort of color pallete I can reference so that things are still a nice and easy color to use.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Those are all my thoughts so far. I&amp;rsquo;ll edit this as my opinions evolve, but I think I need to take a break so that I can look at the site with fresh eyes when I return to it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Primis eget imperdiet lorem</title>
      <link>https://abrac012.github.io/post/post1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abrac012.github.io/post/post1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Example of post with missing date property but with pic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;img&#34; src=&#34;https://abrac012.github.io/images/profile.jpeg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;More text&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;img&#34; src=&#34;https://abrac012.github.io/images/favicon.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://abrac012.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abrac012.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My PhD research focuses on determining the production probabilities of various isotopes resulting from nuclear fission. Better understanding of these production probabilities (formally referred to as Fission Product Yields, or FPYs) has direct implications for nuclear nonproliferation efforts and reactor monitoring &amp;ndash; an increasingly important subject in the wake of rising demand for emissions-free energy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Aside from my graduate school work, I recently interned with and now continue to volunteer for the North Carolina League of Conservation Voters (NCLCV) on the development of North Carolina&amp;rsquo;s renewable energy projects, primarily focusing on energy storage. At NCLCV I authored a critical assessment of Duke Energy&amp;rsquo;s 2024 Integrated Resource Plan where I evaluated their proposals for energy storage development and emphasized the need for and feasibility of larger and more ambitious projects than what is currently proposed. The report will be submitted as a statement of public comment to the North Carolina Public Utilities Commission for the upcoming Integrated Resource Plan cycle.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
