<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Home</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Edits to consider</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/post2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/post2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Okay, so here&amp;rsquo;s what I&amp;rsquo;m thinking&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As far as making a dark theme option, I think the background is already fine for that, but the actual post content isn&amp;rsquo;t. I don&amp;rsquo;t know how to fix that yet, but I&amp;rsquo;m sure there&amp;rsquo;s some sort of color pallete I can reference so that things are still a nice and easy color to use.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Those are all my thoughts so far. I&amp;rsquo;ll edit this as my opinions evolve, but I think I need to take a break so that I can look at the site with fresh eyes when I return to it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fission Product Yields: A Primer on My PhD Thesis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/primer-thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/primer-thesis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Example of post with missing date property but with pic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;img&#34; src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/profile.jpeg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;More text&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;img&#34; src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/favicon.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Okay, here we go:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Within a nuclear reactor&amp;rsquo;s core, a series of highly energetic interactions are happening over and over in quick progession. Neutrons fly, strike fuel nuclei, and ignite an exothermic process that can deliver massive quantities of power at scale. This process, nuclear fission, is considered to be self-sustaining through a chain reaction, like dominoes falling. I&amp;rsquo;ll get into more specifics about all of this later, but there&amp;rsquo;s another character in this story that is often neglected in stories of nuclear power. The neutrino.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
